FAIR AND JUST, LOYAL AND TRUE
YUXI CIGARETTE
Stop looking.
He is not coming.
You should just come with me
to the cement factory.
Let's wait a bit longer.
He told the property management
on the phone
that he would come in person.
Trying to deal with someone like
Song Qingsong, you are still too green.
Just this bag of stuff.
It means nothing to him.
-Why would he come?
-What if he feels guilty?
What if there's something at home
he doesn't want anyone
or the police to find?
I think the one feeling guilty is you.
Keep staring, and you will turn
into Meng Jiangnv.
QINGSONG CEMENT FACTORY, WEIYANG CITY
What are you doing?
That guy dared to harm Wolf.
I am going to cripple him.
Do you even have a brain?
Did you forget we have transformed?
Still talking about knives and guns?
Put it away.
Mr. Jin, you said it yourself,
we were going to deal with him.
Do you know who owns that car
with plate 688?
The boss of Qingsong Cement Factory,
Song Qingsong.
How many lives do you think
you have to mess with him?
So we are not avenging Wolf?
We need to figure out the situation first
before we take revenge.
How did Song Qingsong
get involved with Manlang?
Alright.
That makes sense.
Follow him.
QINGSONG CEMENT FACTORY, WEIYANG CITY
If any words Song Qingsong said were true,
every pig in Weiyang
would be climbing trees.
Criminal Department.
A Mercedes just arrived at the entrance.
They say they are
the owner from Yuanlongli.
Let them in.
-Brigade meeting room.
-Got it.
Come on. We'll be seeing pigs climb trees.
Hey.
Why the rush?
Have you figured out
how to question him about Xu Meng?
Go through every detail
and verify everything.
As long as there are inconsistencies,
we will find a breakthrough.
Song Qingsong
is the victim, not a suspect.
What if he just takes his stuff
and leaves without saying anything?
Tell me, what will you do then?
So what is your plan?
Very simple. Five words.
We will work in tandem.
How?
I lead, you back me up.
I ease him in, you pin him down.
I play the good cop, you play the bad cop.
Got it?
Are you sure
that's really your real intention?
Just tell me. Do you get it or not?
SPECIAL TASK FORCE
The good cop goes first.
What is Song Qingsong
doing at the police station?
Could the police have traced
the Wolf case back to him?
Trace, my foot.
If they had, he'd be here in a police car.
Right.
You just reminded me.
If Song Qingsong
really had dealings with Manlang,
-then we could…
-We can squeeze him for a big payout.
Squeeze your head.
Jeez. We need to think differently.
Use this opportunity
to talk to Song Qingsong.
Get him to throw us some business.
That's called "Water flows downhill,
people move up."
Move up?
What Song Qingsong did before
was way worse than what we did.
I…
If someone like him can clean up his act,
then I should learn from him.
ID and letter of introduction are fine.
This tea tastes terrible.
Wait.
The owner has to come in person
to claim the stolen items.
Call Song Qingsong.
Have him come himself.
Officer,
I have already made it very clear.
The house belongs to my brother-in-law,
but I have been living there recently.
So everything in the safe belongs to me.
Alright. Let's verify everything,
one by one.
What do you mean?
Where were you earlier?
By procedure, we need to confirm
in person that the items are yours
before you can take them.
Please go ahead.
What brand is the liquor?
How many bottles?
Moutai. 53-degree Feitian.
-Four bottles.
-Cigarettes?
Zhonghua. Four cartons.
Four cartons of Zhonghua.
-Yuxi.
-Two cartons.
Two cartons of Yuxi.
Flip-top Yuxi.
Belts?
Two belts.
One gold Rolex.
Three gold rings.
Five gold chains.
Two lighters.
Three bundles of cash.
Bring everything out.
How much cash?
Hundred-yuan bills.
Three bundles. Ten thousand each.
That makes 30,000.
He.
That number sounds familiar.
Yeah, it does.
I heard there's a rule on the street.
Say it's a 40,000-yuan job,
you pay 10,000 upfront,
then the remaining 30 after it's done.
And there's usually a little bonus, right?
At least
two cartons of flip-top Yuxi.
Keep going.
I don't have all day.
Have you checked everything?
Can I go now?
Darn it.
My watch… Where is my gold Rolex?
Where is the money?
-Where is my briefcase?
-What briefcase?
Briefcase… There is no briefcase.
You remembered it wrong.
I am a bit confused.
I have been here too long.
You mean Song Qingsong's briefcase?
No, no. I remembered it wrong.
There wasn't one.
It had "Qingsong Cement"
written on it, right?
I remembered it wrong.
Something in that bag you don't want seen?
Call Song Qingsong.
Tell him the briefcase is missing.
Take the items.
Get to Dahuihuang now.
I still have work.
Is it done now? Can I leave?
Are you sure that's everything?
Nothing else? A watch?
-Cash?
-I am sure.
That is all.
"Build strength."
What is that?
"Forge the police…"
"Build strength, forge the police soul."
You don't recognize the "soul" character?
What does it mean?
Those two characters look a bit creepy.
It has two meanings.
One is ghost, the other is spirit.
-Got it?
-Got it.
I have plenty of spirit.
Whose kid are you?
My dad is He Yuanhang.
That Officer He on secondment.
I have heard of him.
Miss, I need to use the restroom.
Do you know where it is?
Yes. I will take you.
Let's go.
Xiaohe.
Your shoelace is undone. Let me tie it.
Miss, he is looking at your waist.
-Don't go. You're a bad guy.
-Hey.
Kid, you're mistaken.
-Mistaken? Kids don't lie.
-Dad, there's a pervert here!
-What have you done?
-What is going on?
Let go. Is this your child?
None of your business.
Sharp face. Dark circles.
You look kind of creepy.
Like a pervert.
At such a young age,
your temper is already this bad.
You'd better watch yourself
when you grow up.
-Hey!
-I am just telling the truth.
You do need to be careful out there.
He,
when we mentioned the briefcase,
his eyes went right.
When we mentioned the cash,
they shifted left.
He was lying about the briefcase,
but the 30,000 in cash,
he was recalling it.
The one who hired someone
is very likely him.
He should be on his way now
to find Song Qingsong.
Song Qingsong.
Officer He,
if you're going out, leave Xiaohe with me.
I'm Liang Juan from the Analysis Unit.
I'm on the night shift. I can take her
to the cafeteria later.
Thank you, Officer Liang.
-Not at all.
-Kiddo,
I'll come back to pick you up later.
-Listen to Ms. Liang, alright?
-Okay.
So you are the new top graduate
in the Criminal Department.
He is.
Hello.
You two work well together.
Right, Xiaohe?
Let's go.
He's out.
Wait.
He Yuanhang.
The cops are following him.
Should we still follow?
Yes.
He, just the Yuxi cigarettes
and Wu Shanlong's reactions aren't enough.
Even if we follow him
and find Song Qingsong,
we need a plan first.
What plan?
Get him back to the station first,
no matter what.
What? Even a top graduate like you
consults me now?
I have noticed your methods
can be quite effective at times.
There are only three days left.
If we don't use some tactics,
we won't get anywhere.
This missing persons case looks simple,
but the deeper we dig,
the more complicated it gets.
It is like a maze.
A maze?
I do have a theory for that.
Trémaux's algorithm.
Don't even start. My head is spinning.
Is it funny?
Come on. You sing. Go on. Just sing.
Come on, sing it!
Sing.
-Director Li.
-Song Qingsong.
What's your order?
Where are you?
-At the factory.
-At the factory?
Do you know about the mine break-in?
No.
Well, I just got back
from a business trip.
Are the documents still there?
Still there? They have all been taken.
The police are involved now.
I've been told to issue a statement
declaring all the stolen documents
null and void.
Yours too.
Director Li, the documents may be voided,
but my money isn't, right?
Are you out of your mind?
Talking about this on the phone?
Was the mine really robbed?
-Or was it…
-Enough.
Cut the crap. Burn the documents now.
If anyone sees them, it's on you.
Do you hear me?
Hello?
-Again.
-Song Qingsong.
-Another one.
-Do you hear me?
Trying to set me up.
Mr. Liu, where are you now?
Here's the situation.
Something just came up on my end.
My driver lost the documents.
When you arrive, we'll talk…
Liu?
Hello?
DAHUIHUANG NIGHTCLUB
That fool Song Qingsong is not in the car.
Then who is this idiot?
Welcome, boss.
We are glad to have you here.
Wasn't it plate 688?
You sure?
I'm sure.
Mr. Jin, I know someone
who'll remember it better than me.
He.
-He.
-What?
We are just walking in like this?
If not, are we supposed to climb in?
You've done raids here before, have you?
Even if I have, it doesn't stop you
from investigating.
What I mean is,
should we
coordinate a bit?
You lead, I back you up.
You play one role, I play the other.
That one.
This time, you're the one asking me.
What do you mean by "asking"?
We're partners.
Exactly.
On a case, you have to lower yourself
and act naturally.
Let's go.
Welcome, boss.
We are glad to have you here.
Police. Get Ms. Xia over.
Alright.
Mr. Song, I brought it.
Now?
What's the point now?
No, but…
I brought it.
Eight million, and I ended up
with a pile of scrap! Scrap!
Li, you are dead.
Officer He.
Officer He, what brings you here today?
Checking up on us?
Don't worry.
We're running things legally now.
We won't break the rules.
You said that last time.
And the time before.
We have been making improvements.
Let me ask you,
which room is Song Qingsong in?
What Song Qingsong?
Never heard of him.
What about Wu Shanlong?
Which room is Wu Shanlong in?
Officer He, I don't know who they are.
I've never heard of their names.
Ran, make a call.
Get the Public Order Unit over here.
Okay. Maybe we should also call
the fire, commerce, and tax too.
-We should call them all.
-Good idea. Call them all.
-Alright.
-No need.
There's no need to make a fuss over this.
Everyone is tired, right?
Oh my goodness.
What are you still doing here?
Get lost!
Mr. Song, getting angry
is bad for your health.
Who the heck are you?
Mr. Song, they're police.
I'm He Yuanhang from the Nanshan Branch.
I just got off work.
So I brought a colleague out to relax.
We heard you were here,
so we came by to pay a visit.
I cannot stand the cops. Get out.
Song Qingsong, we have received a report
that you solicited prostitution
at Dahuihuang.
Who is making
false accusations against me?
This briefcase contains
the payment, does it not?
The things inside the briefcase
are important documents
from the cement factory.
They're confidential.
Without a warrant,
no one is allowed to touch it.
I will call my superiors right now.
It is a misunderstanding.
It must be.
How could Mr. Song
possibly do such a thing?
Right, I almost forgot.
I have something here
for you to take a look at.
Do you know this woman?
I do not.
Let me remind you.
Muse Foot Massage. Mengmeng.
Just last week, you hit her.
Nonsense.
I never hit women.
Do you have any evidence?
If you have none, get lost.
Mr. Wu,
we didn't get a chance to thank you.
If you hadn't led the way,
how would we have met Mr. Song?
Mr. Song, they came on their own.
You went to the station yourself
to claim the lost items, right?
You said your brother-in-law,
Mr. Song, has treated you well,
so why are you still raking in so much?
Moutai, Zhonghua, a gold Rolex,
and gold chains.
That's over a hundred thousand.
Nonsense. You're slandering me!
Mr. Wu,
you have been very cooperative today.
You told the Criminal Department
a lot about Mr. Song,
especially about that briefcase.
We had no idea it meant so much to him.
Even when Mengmeng merely touched it,
he made sure she disappeared from Weiyang.
You're framing me! Nonsense!
Bastard!
-You bastard!
-You let go!
Qingsong!
-If he goes too far, arrest him.
-They are…
They are clearly trying to drive
a wedge between us.
Assaulting police officers is a crime.
The police are hitting me!
-Qingsong, run!
-Stop right there.
-Let go.
-Qingsong, run!
-Stop.
-Qingsong.
Vice squad!
-Run!
-Vice raid! Run!
Hurry! Run!
Is that him? Right?
-No. Not him.
-Is that him?
This way.
Leave now!
Mr. Jin.
The one who climbed down the pipe.
That is him! That is him!
You still recognize him
with that injury on his head?
Mr. Jin, I never forget a face.
-Bring him here. Hurry.
-Alright.
DAHUIHUANG NIGHTCLUB
-He, drive.
-Mr. Jin.
Police.
Fuck.
One after another.
What is this, Snake?
Behind us.
Son of a bitch!
Faster. Go faster.
This is just a Fukang.
He's driving a Benz.
If Song Qingsong gets away this time,
it will be hard to find him again.
Song Qingsong,
I will not let you get away.
He, don't lose your head. Be careful.
At this point, whoever eases off loses.
He's cutting me off.
Then I'll cut him off too.
If there's an accident,
we'll bring both him and the car in.
That works.
He, accelerate.
Benz, here I come.
Come on.
It won't move?
Hurry up.
-I can't move it!
-They're gone.
Song Qingsong, you scoundrel!
You wrecked my car. I'm not done with you!
Wu Shanlong,
didn't you say it was in the safe?
What a coincidence
that the thief just happened to take it.
Wu Shanlong, are you playing me?
Stop yelling at me.
Everyone has been yelling at me today.
I'm telling you,
even if we got the documents,
they're useless now.
Useless?
What do you mean? Explain.
Dongshan Mine was robbed.
You know that, right?
The bidding documents were inside.
Song Qingsong is furious.
He spent eight million
on a pile of worthless paper.
You want to blackmail him
with that pile of worthless paper?
The police came just now.
They seem to be onto Mengmeng.
If Song Qingsong gets arrested,
neither of us is getting out of this.
What do we do now?
I know what to do.
Hello?
QINGSONG CEMENT
FAIR AND JUST, LOYAL AND TRUE
SPECIAL TASK FORCE MEMBER LIST
-Xiaohe.
What major case is it this time?
Four teenagers went missing
in Binchuan District.
They still have not been found.
Now the municipal bureau
is forming a special task force.
Our district has to assist.
Didn't they call you to join?
Enough chatting. Meeting.
We will go up first.
Xiaohe, you're finally here.
Captain Zhao has been looking for you.
-For me?
-Go on.
APPROVED
-Captain Zhao.
-Come in.
APPROVED BY ZHAO JIE
Sit.
Xiaohe,
about Han Zi'ang's case,
I plan to assign it to you.
Han Zi'ang's case?
What about the one in Binchuan District?
What, you think
this case isn't big enough?
Of course not.
I wouldn't dare pick and choose.
Captain, don't worry.
I will make sure this case
is thoroughly investigated.
About this case, Captain Qu
wrote a report yesterday.
You can refer to it.
Okay.
From what we can tell,
it's most likely a prank.
So, the focus is on cleanup
and calming the parents.
Understood?
CAPTAIN'S OFFICE
One more thing.
Sort out your family matters
as soon as possible.
See? I told you.
By seniority,
Zhao Jie is still just a kid to me.
He Yuanhang,
you should give up on that idea.
I will not let you,
or any of you, get involved in this case.
Just treat me and Mr. Ran as helpers.
No need to feed us. We won't steal credit.
All upside.
If you keep causing trouble,
I'll transfer back to the archives
-and sit there doing nothing.
-No, no.
I'm begging you. Please.
Help Mr. Ran, okay?
There is nothing I can do to help him.
He Xiaohe, that is Mr. Ran.
He watched you grow up.
Have you forgotten how good he was to you?
I have not.
He's doing quite well now.
Stop bothering him.
It's not good for either of you.
He's just pretending he's fine.
Since I came back, I have looked into it.
I found that he's still avoiding
that case from back then.
It's his demon.
We need to help him face it.
-Face it?
-Right.
-And then?
-Then,
he stays in Weiyang
and rejoins the Criminal Department.
You're dreaming again.
He's a university lecturer now.
Can he just be transferred back
to the Criminal Department?
Besides, he's doing great in Beijing.
Why do you insist
on bringing him back to Weiyang?
That's for later.
Right now, let's talk
about the helpers thing.
I'll be honest with you.
Captain Zhao assigned this case
to me not because of you.
Everyone thinks it's a prank.
Barely even a case.
What?
What kind of logic is that?
Back when Xu Meng
and her father went missing,
everyone said it was a prank too.
Was it?
Dad,
stop dwelling on the past.
Go home.
I've got work.
Hey!
FAIR AND JUST, LOYAL AND TRUE
Master!
Master, thank you.
I really should have
listened to you yesterday
and gone straight to Yuanlongli.
Would've saved a lot of trouble.
Thank you so much.
-Thank you.
-It's nothing.
No big deal.
How's your child?
He is still unconscious.
The police say he attacked
someone with a knife.
How is that possible?
The school wants to expel him.
I really don't know what to do.
But he did attack someone.
Did anyone actually see it?
Bring that person out
and let them face me.
I want to see who it was
that knocked him unconscious.
Master,
you are experienced.
Please do a reading for me.
See whether my child
can get through this safely.
I don't do fortune-telling.
I only find people.
Then please help me find the culprit.
How about I find you an expert?
If he takes the case,
your child's situation will definitely
be thoroughly investigated.
I'll do whatever you say.
Wait here, I'll call him out.
Thank you, Master. Thank you.
He really is remarkable.
Hurry up. The mother is waiting.
Move it.
You're so careless.
Ms. Wang, I have been looking
for you. Get in the car.
Officer He, I'm waiting for someone.
Han Zi'ang's case is now under my charge.
If you want to find out the truth,
come with me.
-But…
-Hurry, get in.
-Alright.
-Kiddo.
Kiddo.
Ms. Wang, don't worry too much
about your son's case.
The victim only has minor injuries.
It's considered a light offense.
Trust us.
We'll get to the truth.
Ang is innocent.
He's so young.
If he grows up carrying that,
what will people think of him?
He's in a private school now.
Look at me.
I pulled strings and spent
a lot of money to get him in.
If he gets expelled,
our lives will be ruined.
I'll go to the school tomorrow
and speak to the principal.
Thank you. Thank you, Officer.
But I have one condition.
Go ahead.
Stop seeing that old man.
Master?
-Why?
-He's no master. He's my dad.
He's a fraud.
You've got some nerve.
You tricked Song Qingsong?
You think someone like him
is that easy to trick?
He's suspicious.
Just a few looks
and you call him a suspect?
Where is the evidence? No evidence,
and now it's backfired on you.
The traffic police called me.
They said a Mercedes driver
reported you for rear-ending him.
He wants 30,000.
How much?
Thirty thousand.
-Done?
-Don't touch it.
It's not dry yet.
I'm not letting this go
with Song Qingsong.
Keep an eye on Xiaohe.
I'm going to stake out the cement factory.
He.
I was impulsive yesterday.
-I'm afraid…
-Afraid of what?
I'm not afraid of anyone.
Dad, is that the bad guy who hit our car?
I'm going too!
Kiddo, be good.
Stay with Uncle Ran today.
I'll pick you up later.
Don't worry. I am not being impulsive.
I have to keep an eye on Song Qingsong.
-If not, he'll slip away.
-He.
If we can't get him soon,
we'll have no other leads.
I want to try that maze theory.
We've only got two days left.
Try whatever theory you've got.
-I'm heading out.
-Hey!
Be careful.
Officer Ran,
this is Luandongzi's statement.
-We need you to verify it.
-Thank you.
QUESTION: HOW DID YOU GET IN YUANLONGLI?
ANSWER: YOU'VE CAME TO THE RIGHT PERSON
There's an underground garage
at Yuanlongli?
Yes.
Luandongzi said people who pass by there
can avoid the cameras at
the security booth and building entrance.
YUANLONGLI INTERNATIONAL GARDEN
Officer Ran,
the entrance to this underground garage
was sealed a few years ago.
There's only this small access door now.
You need a key.
Where is the exit?
Outside the compound. Also needs a key.
Besides the property management,
who else has keys?
Not sure.
You'll have to ask Manager Qian.
Officer Ran, I need to get back
to the CCTV room.
I'll leave you here.
All the keys for New York Block are here.
Return them to the property office
when you're done.
-Thank you.
-You are welcome.
I'm heading off.
-Bye.
-Okay.
Xiaohe.
Uncle Ran,
this underground maze is so cool.
Stay close.
There might be rats running out.
I'm not afraid of rats.
I caught one this big at my grandma's.
Xiaohe.
Uncle Ran. I caught a big rat!
What are you doing? Let go!
Who are you?
-Stop shining that light!
-Manager Qian?
What are you doing here?
Someone reported
that the motion lights are broken.
I came to fix them.
SAFETY FIRST
Does an electrician's work
need the property manager to handle?
Oh, come on.
Uncle Ran, don't believe him.
He looks more like a thief.
Watch your mouth.
Whose daughter are you?
Officer He's daughter.
No wonder.
Your dad and I are good friends.
You should be calling me Mr. Qian.
Save it. I'm not friends with a thief.
You!
Officer Ran,
what are you doing down here?
Stop coughing.
That penny-pincher
turned off the motion lights.
-Why?
-To save electricity.
Tell me, what is he doing
with all that cement?
-Building a grave at home?
-You two!
Did you hear that?
What was that sound?
Could it be those two missing people?
Are you serious?
You two!
-Oh my goodness!
-Who is it?
Don't scare me. I'm afraid of the dark!
You two, get out here now!
Why aren't you at work?
What are you doing down here? For what?
Didn't you tell us to…
I… Tell…
Tell what?
Get back to work!
Wait.
You dropped something.
Officer Ran, I still have things
to do at the property office.
I'll be heading up now too.
Hold on.
Besides the property management,
who else has the key to the garage?
When Yuanlongli was first built,
there weren't many cars.
The vehicle entrance was sealed off.
At that time,
only the property management had the key.
But then, later on,
the Pattia Club opened.
They were afraid of resident complaints,
so they had their guests
and staff use the garage.
The keys just couldn't be tracked anymore.
Officer Ran,
-I… I'll be going…
-Just go. Mr. Penny-pincher.
You really take after your dad.
SAFETY FIRST